<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS and Octank on Octank Offshore Supply Chain</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS and Octank on Octank Offshore Supply Chain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 10:40:29 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Problem</title>
      <link>/octank/businessproblem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 10:36:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/octank/businessproblem/</guid>
      <description>How do we reduce costs and improve efficiency in the managed supply chain?
Specifically, how do we help Martin, a engineer and planner, with three tasks:
 Capacity planning and insight into utilization Inventory management and identifying common joint tasks Forecasting demand and predicting supply needs  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>/octank/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 10:24:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/octank/architecture/</guid>
      <description>In the last meeting, we whiteboarded a solution for Martin based on an event-driven serverless architecture.
Principles Modern, event driven solution that lays the foundation for further development. The solution should require as little overhead as possible.
Well Architected Framework The goal was to design a solution specific to this use-case but also flexible enough to evolve over time. Additionally, the solution must follow all of the well architected framework pillars:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demonstration</title>
      <link>/octank/demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 10:25:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/octank/demo/</guid>
      <description>Click below to go to the QuickSight Dashboard.
Let&amp;rsquo;s go!  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cost and Timeline</title>
      <link>/octank/cost/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 10:24:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/octank/cost/</guid>
      <description>Next Steps Supply Chain Visibility POC This is a cost estimate for implementation and ongoing costs for one Offshore facility. Costs are estimated in US dollars for the US-East-1 region. The estimates do not include fees, taxes, or Octank Enterprise Discounts. The actual costs depend on a variety of factors, including the project scope and actual usage of AWS services.
Timeline and Implementation Costs gantt dateFormat YYYY-MM-DD title Notional implementation timeline section Business tasks Demonstration :done, des1, 2020-09-20, 1d Project scoping :active, des2, after des1, 10d Kickoff :des3, after des2, 1d Build and Delivery :des4, after des3, 26d POC Closeout &amp; Next Steps :des5, after des4, 2d section IT tasks Data access and testing :crit, cri1, after des2, 14d IT support for build and delivery :crit, cri2, after des2, 21d Security testing and IRM reviews :crit, after cri2, 5d     Resources Time in weeks Costs     Business Owner 6    IT Architect 3    IT Developer 3    AWS ProServe Engagement Manager 6 $115,920   AWS ProServe Architect 6 $115,920   AWS ProServe Developer 6 $87,360   Total  $319,200    Ongoing costs    Service Monthly First 12 months total Configuration summary     Amazon Athena $ 297.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extending the Concept</title>
      <link>/octank/extendible/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 10:25:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/octank/extendible/</guid>
      <description>The solution is the start of a journey. It is designed to be extendible without creating Technical Debt.
Specifically, it is designed to:
 Ingest additional data sources Support additional presentation layers Integrate current and future AI/ML models  Amazon Alexa An example of the extendibility would be adding a voice interface so that Martin could get updates and ask questions in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/octank/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 15:42:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/octank/resources/</guid>
      <description>AWS Energy blogs:  How to analyze well drilling reports using natural language processing Interpreting 3D seismic data automatically using Amazon SageMaker  AWS Petrophysics videos: Porosity Prediction with Amazon SageMaker&amp;rsquo;s XGBoost Algorithm   Lithology Prediction in Oil &amp;amp; Gas with Amazon SageMaker   Seismic Density Prediction in Oil &amp;amp; Gas with Amazon SageMaker   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>